No way.
A waterproof boot cover can protect your
shoe from mud and splashes. Okay?
Let's go. So, here is how it looks. You
can see there's leather on the bottom.
There is a zip here and there are two
light reflectors, this one and this one.
Let's go. Well, because I want to test
this thoroughly, I'm going to put in
some white socks and some white shoes.
Now, let's put in the second one.
I truly have to tell you this is
comfortable. Now, let's go outside.
>> [laughter]
>> YES, SIR.
YEAH.
LOOK AT THIS ONE IS OUT.
HOW ABOUT WE TRY THIS?
>> [groaning]
>> NOW, we're just going to use some clean
water
and wash it off.
Let's see what happened. All right, let
me take this this boot out
and see if our white shoe is clean. 3 2
1, let's go.
WHAT?
OH.
YES, SIR.
YO, THERE'S NOT ONE stain on it, bro.
It's totally clean, bro. It's totally
clean.
Shoo.
Let's go. Guys, this is a W. You can see
how it protected my shoe and I don't
even have a stain on it. And everything
is still completely fine. To get this,
just click on the link in my bio and
don't forget to follow for more.
Yeah.